我最近又在想着时光旅行的事了
you know,I've been thinking about time travel again.
为什么 你又撞上看不见的障碍物了?
Why,did you hit a roadblock with invisibility?
先不说那个
Put it on the back burner.
我想到 如果我发明了完美的时间机器
Anyway,it occurs to me if I ever did perfect a time machine,
我会回到过去把它送给自己
I would just go into the past and give it to myself,
省得要自己再去发明它一次
thus eliminating the need for me to invent it in the first place.
不错
Interesting.
是啊 这样能让我减压不少
Yeah,it really takes the pressure off.
听起来像是个大突破
Sounds like a breakthrough.
要我打电话给科学杂志 让他们留下头版的位置吗?
Should I call science magazine and tell them to hold the cover?
这可是时间旅行 莱纳德 过去的我已经打过了
It's time travel,leonard,I will have already done that.
那我想就等着祝贺你啦
Then I guess congratulations are in order.
不 过去的你已经祝贺过我了
No,congratulations will have been in order.
我肯定在派对上不会开心的
You know,I am not going to enjoy this party.
我知道 我太了解你
I know,I'm familiar with you.
上次系里的派对 芬克顿教授抓着我
The last department party,professor finkleday cornered me
讨论洞穴探险 一直说了45分钟
and talked about spelunking for 45 minutes.
是的 我也在场
Yes,I was there.
你知道窑洞有什么意思吗 莱纳德?
You know what's interesting about caves,leonard?
- 什么? - 什么也没有
- What? - Nothing.
那我们躲开他 去见到新的系主任
Well,then we'll avoid finkleday,we'll meet the new department head,
恭喜他 跟他握手 然后就走
congratulate him,shake his hand and go.
这样如何?
How's this?
"见到你很高兴 盖博豪斯博士"
"Pleased to meet you,dr.Gablehauser.
"您真幸运 学校雇了你做系主任"
"How fortunate for you that the university's "chosen to hire you,
"尽管您25年来都没做出什么原创研究"
despite the fact "that you've done no original research in 25 years,
"而只是出版了一系列畅销书"
"and instead have written a series of popular books "
"将科学的伟大概念 降格为一系列奇闻轶事"
that reduce the great concepts of science "to a series of anecdotes,
"每则故事都简单到
"each one dumbed down to accommodate the duration
能在一次肠部运动的时间内看完" (就是厕所读物)
of an average bowel movement.
Mahalo (夏威夷语的谢谢)
Mahalo.
"Mahalo"是不错的修饰
"Mahalo's" a nice touch.
你知道夏威夷语里只有8个辅音吗?
You know there only eight consonants in the hawaiian language?
很好 你就这么做开场白吧
Interesting. You should lead with that.
瞧瞧这自助餐
Oh,god,look at this buffet.
我爱美国
I love america.
印度没自助餐吗?
You don't have buffets in india?
当然有 可那些都是印度菜
Of course,but it's all indian food.
在孟买你可能连救命的面包圈都找不到
You can't find a bagel in mumbai to save your life.
给我涂点
Shmear me.
真是有趣
Well,here's an interesting turn of events.
怎么了?
What?
霍华德带了女伴?
Howard brought a date?
最有可能性的解释是
A more plausible explanation is
他在机器人方面的研究 取得了重大进展
that his work in robotics has made an amazing leap forward.
怎样 科学怪人们?
Hey,what up,science bitches?
这位是我特别的女性朋友桑茉
May I introduce my special lady friend summer?
霍华德 我说了碰我要加钱的
Howard,I told you touching's extra.
好 抱歉
Right. Sorry.
我们的新老板来了 礼貌点
Here comes our new boss. Be polite.
大家好
Hi,fellas.
- 我是艾瑞克·盖博豪斯 - 我是霍华德·沃罗威茨
- Eric gablehauser. - Howard wolowitz.
霍华德 见到你很高兴 你是?
Howard,nice to meet you. And you are?
一个真真正正的科学家
An actual real scientist.
这个开场白怎样?
How was that?
我不敢相信他开除我了
I can't believe he fired me.
你说他是被捧出来的高中理科老师
Well,you did call him a glorified high school science teacher
还说他上一次成功的试验 是点燃了自己的屁
whose last successful experiment was lighting his own farts.
但我之前说了"恕我直言"
In my defense,I prefaced that by saying,"with all due respect."
《生活大爆炸》
第一季  第04集
The.Luminous.Fish.Effect
早
Morning.
今天早餐 你做鸡蛋吃?
You're making eggs for breakfast?
这不是早餐 这是试验
This isn't breakfast,it's an experiment.
但看起来很像早餐
'Cause it looks a lot like breakfast.
我终于有时间验证我的理论 从蛋白质中分离水分子
I finally have time to test my hypothesis about the separation of the water molecules
以及它对口感的影响
from the egg proteins and its impact vis-a-vis taste.
听起来真开胃
Sounds yummy.
我很期待你配上熏肉后的成果
I look forward to your work with bacon.
我也是
As do I.
我相信只要你跟盖博豪斯道歉
You know,I'm sure if you just apologize to gablehauser,
他会让你回去工作的
he would give you your job back.
我不想回去工作
I don't want my job back.
过去三年半时间我都在瞪着 写满方程式的板子上
I've spent the past three and a half years staring at grease boards full of equations.
在那之前我花了四年时间写论文
Before that,I spent four years working on my thesis.
在那之前 我在上大学 而在大学之前 我在上5年级
Before that,I was in college,and before that,I was in the fifth grade.
这是我十几年来第一次休息 我要好好享受
This is my first d oayff in decades and I'm going to savor it.
好吧
Okay.
那你回去弄你的鸡蛋吧
I'll let you get back to fixing your eggs.
不只是我的鸡蛋 弄的是全人类的蛋
Not just fixing my eggs,I'm fixing everyone's eggs.
我们都感激你
And we all thank you.
要用新鲜鸡蛋
use new eggs.
嗨 我正要去超市
hi. Hey,I'm running out to the market.
你们要带什么吗?
Do you guys need anything?
这就是那些不熟悉数学规律的人
Oh,well,this would be one of those circumstances that
会称之为巧合的事件之一了
people unfamiliar with the law of large numbers would call a coincidence.
你说什么?
I'm sorry?
我要蛋
I need eggs.
4打就够了
Four dozen should suffice.
4打?
Four dozen?
对 棕蛋 白蛋
Yes,and evenly distributed amongst brown,white,
走地鸡蛋 大鸡蛋 加大鸡蛋 跟特大鸡蛋各要8个
free-range,large,extra large and jumbo.
好 再说一次
Okay,one more time.
算了 你肯定搞不对
Never mind. You won't get it right.
我最好跟你一起去
I'd better come with you.
好呀
Oh,yay.
你今天怎么没去上班?
How come you didn't go into work today?
我在休假 因为我不愿向平庸之流屈服
I'm taking a sabbatical because I won't kowtow to mediocre minds.
你给开除了?
So you got canned,huh?
理论上说物理学家不会给开除...
Theoretical physicists do not get canned...
但你说对了
but yeah.
可能这样最好
Well,maybe it's all for the best.
我相信一扇门关上了  总会有另外一扇门打开的
You know,I always say when one door closes,another one opens.
不 不是的
No,it doesn'T.
除非两扇门用继电器连接
Not unless the two doors are connected by relays
而且还装有传感器
or there are motion sensors involved.
不 我是说...
No,no,I meant...
或者一扇门关上时产生的空气
or if the first door closing creates a change of air pressure
压力作用于第二扇门引致...
that acts upon the second door.
算了
Never mind.
慢点
Slow down.
慢点! 拜托慢点!
Slow down. Please,slow down!
没事啦!
We're fine!
你跟车都不保持足够的距离
You're not leaving yourself enough space between cars.
我有啊!
Oh,sure,I am.
不 我给你算算
No,no,let me do the math for you.
就算这车重4000磅
This car weighs,let's say 4,000 pounds.
我140磅 你120磅
Now add 140 for me,120 for you...
- 120? - 不好意思
- 120? - Oh,I'm sorry.
冒犯你了吗?
Did I insult you?
你的体重跟自我价值有关系?
Is your body mass somehow tied into your self-worth?
当然
Well,yeah.
有趣
Interesting.
那么我们就算总重4400磅吧
Anyway,that gives us a total weight of,let's say 4,400 pounds.
算4390磅
Let's say 4,390.
好
Fine.
目前时速是 老天啊 51英里/时
We're traveling forward at-- good lord-- 51 miles an hour.
假设你的刹车是新的 卡钳也是校准的
Now let's assume that your brakes are new and the calipers are aligned.
当我们踩下刹车时
Still,by the time we come to a stop,
我们就会和前面的别克汽车撞在一起
we'll be occupying the same space as that buick in front of us,
因此我们会在短时间内 给压成稀泥 死得很惨...
an impossibility that nature will quickly resolve into death,mutilation...
哇 看 他们在铺新的迷你高尔夫场地
oh,look,they built a new putt-putt course.
真不错
This is great.
看看我
Look at me.
我生活在普通人的平凡世界中
I'm in the real world of ordinary people
过着他们无趣平常的一天
just living their ordinary,colorless workaday lives.
谢谢
Thank you.
不 谢谢你
No,thank you.
还有谢谢你 普通人
And thank you,ordinary person.
你想知道关于番茄的趣闻吗?
Hey,you want to hear an interesting thing about tomatoes?
不 不是很想
Uh,no,no,not really.
你不是要买鸡蛋的吗?
Listen,didn't you say you needed some eggs?
对 但任何对细菌繁殖学稍有了解的人
Yes,but anyone who knows anything about the dynamics of bacterial growth
都会在出去结账时 才买冰柜里的食物
knows to pick up their refrigerated foods on the way out of the supermarket.
那好 那你现在就该准备出去了
Oh,okay,well,then maybe you should start heading on out then.
不 这样很好玩啊
No,this is fun.
关于番茄的事 我觉得你肯定会喜欢的
Oh,the thing about tomatoes-- and I think you'll really enjoy this--
它们给摆在蔬菜栏里 但事实上却是一种水果
is they're shelved with the vegetables,but they're technically a fruit.
- 真有意思 - 是吧?
- Oh,interesting. - Isn't it?
不 我指的是你觉得有趣的事情很有趣
No,I mean what you find enjoyable.
天啊
Oh,boy.
又怎么了?
What now?
服用维生素剂虽然有一定好处
Well,there's some value to taking a multivitamin,
但人体能吸收的量是有限的
but the human body can only absorb so much.
你买这么多 就是买的一堆昂贵的尿液原料
What you're buying here are the ingredients for very expensive urine.
也许那就是我的目的呢
Well,maybe that's what I was going for.
那你可以买锰
Well,then you'll want some manganese.
刚刚很好玩呀
Well,that was fun.
也许明天我们能 一起去那种仓储式商店
Maybe tomorrow we can go to one of those big warehouse stores.
我不知道哦 谢尔顿
Oh,I don't know,sheldon.
我要花一段时间才能 从今天度过的乐趣中恢复过来
It's going to take me a while to recover from all the fun I had today.
你确定?
Are you sure?
大宗采购有很多优势呀
There are a lot of advantages to buying in bulk.
比如说 我发现你的卫生巾一次是购买一个月的量
For example,I noticed that you purchase your tampons one-month supply at a time.
什么?
What?
想想啊
Think about it.
这种东西放着也不会变坏
It's a product that doesn't spoil
而且你接下来至少30年都要用它
and you're going to be needing them for at least the next 30 years.
你要我一次性买30年份的?
You want me to buy 30 years worth of tampons?
30或35年 你母亲什么时候绝经的?
Well,30,35. When did your mother go into menopause?
好了
Okay.
我才不跟你说这个
I'm not talking about this with you.
这是很自然的人类进程
Oh,penny,this is a natural human process
而且我们讨论怎么省钱的问题
and we're talking about statistically significant savings.
现在假设你每次用15条 28天一周期...
Now,if you assume 15 tampons per cycle and a 28-day cycle...
你经期正常吗?
are you fairly regular?
好吧 不去仓储式商店 但我们还是一起去高尔夫 对吧
Okay,no warehouse store,but we're still on for putt-putt golf,right?
我刚碰到佩里
Hey,I just ran into penny.
她好像有点心烦
She seemed upset about something.
可能她大姨妈来了吧
I think it's her time of the month.
我在日历上做记录 以备参考
I marked the calendar for future reference.
鱼是怎么回事?
What's with the fish?
是实验呀
It's an experiment.
你的炒蛋研究呢?
What happened to your scrambled egg research?
那是死路一条
Oh,that was a dead end.
炒蛋怎么弄也就这样啦
Scrambled eggs are as good as they're ever going to be.
那...现在研究鱼?
So... fish?
我看到一篇文章 说日本科学家
I read an article about japanese scientists
将发光水母的DNA注入到其他动物体内
who inserted dna from luminous jellyfish into other animals
我就想 "哦 夜光鱼"
and I thought,"hey,fish nightlights.
夜光鱼?
Fish nightlights?
这是个能发大财的主意
It's a billion-dollar idea.
我不会出去
Mum's the word.
谢尔顿 你确定不要跟
Sheldon,are you sure you don't want to
系主任道歉 然后回去上班啊?
just apologize to gablehauser and get your job back?
不不不 我有太多事情要做
Oh,no,no,no,I have too much to do.
比如说发光鱼
Like luminous fish.
对不起 我不知道
I'm sorry. I didn'T...
这只是个开头
that's just the beginning.
我还有个大宗女性护理用品 邮购公司的设想
I also have an idea for a bulk mail-order feminine hygiene company.
夜光卫生棉条!
Oh,glow-in-the-dark tampons!
莱纳德 我们会暴富
Leonard,we're gonna be rich.
谢谢你这么快赶过来
Thanks for coming on such short notice.
你给我打电话是对的
Well,you did the right thing calling.
我不知道还能怎么办
I didn't know what else to do.
他失去生活的重心了
He's lost all focus.
每天他都沉迷于一个新想法
Every day he's got a new obsession.
这一个让我特别困扰
This is a particularly disturbing one.
妈妈?
Mommy?
宝贝!
Hi,baby!
你给我妈打电话了?!
你给自己弄了个纺织机? 真棒!
Oh,you got yourself a loom? How nice!
谢谢
Thank you.
亲爱的 为什么要弄台纺织机?
Honey,why'd you get a loom?
我在研究发光鱼 所以我想到...
I was working with luminous fish,and I thought,hey...
"纺织机" (英语中"纺织机"与"发光"发音部分相同)
"loom."
你来这干嘛 妈妈?
Mom,what are you doing here?
莱纳德给我打电话了
Leonard called me.
我知道 为什么?
I know,but why?
因为21世纪最聪明的脑袋
Because one of the great minds of the 21st century
用在了养夜光鱼 和编织毛毯上
is raising glow-in-the-dark fish and weaving serapes.
这不是披肩 这是披风
This is not a serape,this is a poncho.
披肩两边不收边 披风是一体的
A serape is open at the sides; a poncho is closed.
所以这是披风
This is a poncho.
不管是什么 都不能成为 你打电话给别人母亲的理由
And neither is a reason to call someone's mother.
是吗? 你上一次出门是什么时候?
Really? When was the last time you left the house?
跟佩里去超市
I went to the market with penny.
对 那是三周以前的事了
Yeah,that was three weeks ago.
那么小心啦 接下来的4到8天她会变得很暴躁
Well,then buckle up-- in the next four to eight days she's going to get very crabby.
亲爱的 你的朋友很担心你
Sweetheart,your little friend is concerned about you.
但我是成年人了 我能过自己想要的生活
Yes,well,I'm not a child-- I'm a grown man,capable of living my life as I see fit.
我也绝不需要 有打小报告人给我的妈妈!
And I certainly don't need someone telling on me to my mother!
等等 你去哪?
Wait,where are you going?
我房间! 所有人都不许进来!
To my room-- and no one's allowed in!
他的脾气像他爸爸
oh,he gets his temper from his daddy.
- 眼睛像我 - 原来如此
- He's got my eyes. - I see.
他的科学头脑是上帝赐予的
All that science stuff,that comes from jesus.
谢尔顿 你妈妈做了晚饭
Sheldon,your mom made dinner.
我不饿!
I'm not hungry!
莱纳德 你别管了 他很固执的
Oh,leonard,don't trouble yourself. He's stubborn.
他会一直待到他满意为止
He may stay in there till the rapture.
确定那是件坏事?
We so sure that's a bad thing?
跟你说 我很爱那孩子 但他很难相处
I tell you,I love the boy to death,but he has been difficult
自从他在Kmart超市 从我身体里滑出来后
since he fell out of me at the k-mart.
原谅我的无礼 但我终于知道谢尔顿 英俊的外表是从哪继承的了
Excuse me for being so bold,but I now see where sheldon gets his smoldering good looks.
亲爱的 这不会起作用的 但你可以继续尝试
Honey,that ain't gonna work,but you keep tryin'.
我做了鸡肉
I made chicken.
我希望你们那里 不会把他当做神圣的动物
I hope that isn't one of the animals that you people think is magic.
我们教堂里有一个印度人
You know,we have an indian gentleman at our church,
派特医生 这是个感人的故事
a dr.Patel-- it's a beautiful story.
上帝给与他启示 把他带来我们身边 让我们享受8折手术
The lord spoke to him and moved him to give us all 20% off on lasik--
你知道 给那些需要做这手术的人
you know,those that needed it.
真是个感人的故事
That is a lovely story.
谢尔顿的事 我们不用做什么吗?
Um,are we gonna do anything about sheldon?
当然要
Oh,we will.
对付谢尔顿要慢慢来
You have to take your time with sheldon.
他死去的爸爸过去总跟我说
His father,god rest his soul,used to always say to me,
"玛丽 对谢尔顿要耐心"
"mary,you have to take your time with sheldon."
听起来是个睿智的人啊
Sounds like a wise man.
没那么睿智
Oh,not so wise.
他有一次为了甘草跟山猫打了一架
He once tried to fight a bobcat for some licorice.
大家拿盘子 还有谢尔顿织的餐垫
So,everybody grab a plate and a pretty place mat that shelly wove.
他以前也这么发作过吗?
Has shelly ever freaked out like this before?
总是这样
Oh,all the time.
我记得他13岁时的夏天
I remember one summer when he was 13,
他在小屋里做了一个小型原子反应堆
he built a small nuclear reactor in the shed
然后跟大家说 他会为全镇人提供免费电力
and told everybody he was gonna provide free electricity for the whole town.
问题是 他没有你们所说的"可裂变物质"
Well,the only problem was,he had no what you call "fissionable" materials.
当他试图上网采购时
Anyway,when he went on the internets to get some,
一个政府官员来访 很温柔地让他坐下
a man from the government came by and sat him down real gentle,
告诉他 私人持有铀精矿是违法的
and told him it's against the law to have yellow-cake uranium in a shed.
然后呢?
Well,what happened?
发作了呀
Well,poor boy had a fit.
把自己锁在屋里 做了个音速死亡放射线仪
Locked himself in his room and built a sonic death ray.
死亡放射线?
A death ray?
他是这么叫的
Well,that's what he called it.
那玩意都阻止不了隔壁的小孩
Didn't even slow down the neighbor kids.
倒是让家里的狗折腾个没完
It pissed our dog off to no end.
知道吗 你俩真是可爱的一对
You know,you two make a cute couple.
不 我们不是...
uh,no. We're not...
不是一对 我们都是单身
we're not-not a couple. We're singles.
- 两个单身 - 对
- Two singles. - Yeah.
像是那种...独立包装的芝士片
Like those... individually wrapped slices of cheese that...
我们是朋友
we're friends.
我是不是踩到地雷了?
Did I pluck a nerve there?
- 对 - 好吧
- Oh,yeah. - Okay.
好吧 大家 该吃饭了
All right,everybody,it's time to eat.
主啊 感谢您赐予我们晚餐 及您所有的恩赐
Oh,lord,we thank you for this meal and all of your bounty.
我们祈求您帮助谢尔顿重新振作
And we pray that you help sheldon get back on his rocker.
沉思一阵之后 我会以"以主之名"结束
Now,after a moment of silent meditation,I'm gonna end with "in jesus' name,"
但你们俩不一定要跟着一起说
but you two don't feel any obligation to join in.
当然 除非你被圣灵感动
Unless,of course,the holy spirit moves you.
哇 这是我吃过最好吃的厚皮馅饼
Oh,my god,this is the best cobbler I've ever had.
谢尔顿最喜欢吃这个
It was always sheldon's favorite.
你知道秘方是什么吗?
You know w thathe secret ingredient is?
- 爱? - 猪油
- Love? - Lard.
看看谁来了...
Hey,look who's come...
嘘 你会吓到他的
You'll spook him.
他就跟小鹿似的 你得让他过来亲近你
He's like a baby deer-- you got to let him come to you.
太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
够了! 谢尔顿 振作起来!
Damn it,sheldon,snap out of it!
你是物理学家
You're a physicist--
该在学校做实验 而不是躲房间里
you belong at the university doing research,not hiding in your room!
你不打猎的 是不是?
you don't hunt,do you?
早上好 小饼干
good morning,snickerdoodle.
早
Morning.
那看起来好奇特啊 是什么呢?
Oh,well,that looks awful fancy. What is that?
我设想的硅系生物DNA模型
It's my idea of what dna would look like in a silicon-based life-form.
但是由造物主巧妙地设计?
But intelligently designed by a creator,right?
你想干什么呀 妈妈?
What do you want,mom?
你知道你爸爸经常说
You know how your daddy used to say that
你只能在把炸药扔进鱼塘之前
you can only fish for so long
钓那么一会儿鱼
before you got to throw a stick of dynamite in the water?
记得
Yeah.
我钓够鱼了
Well,I'm done fishing.
你穿上衣服
You put those on.
为什么?
What for?
因为你要回到办公室
Because you're gonna go down to your office,
跟你的老板道歉 回去上班
you're gonna apologize to your boss and get your job back.
不要
No.
不好意思 我刚刚是以 "若尊贵的陛下愿意"开始的吗?
I'm sorry,did I start that sentence with the words,"if it please your highness"?
我不要道歉 我说的都是实话
I'm not going to apologize-- I didn't say anything that wasn't true.
你听好
Now,you listen here.
我从你4岁开始就跟你说
I have been telling you since you were four years old,
比大家都聪明不是问题 但你不能到处显摆
it's okay to be smarter than everybody,but you can't go around pointing it out.
为什么?
Why not?
因为别人不喜欢!
Because people don't like it!
记得邻居的孩子欺负你的事吗?
Remember all the ass-kickings you got from the neighbor kids?
动作快点
now,let's get crackin'.
沐浴更衣 然后我们就出发
Shower,shirt,shoes,and let's shove off.
如果那该死的死亡放射线能用 我就不会挨打了
There wouldn't have been any ass-kickings if that stupid death ray had worked.
问题解决了
Problem solved.
真的?
Really?
真厉害
That's impressive.
莱纳德 主自有分寸
Leonard,the lord never gives us more than we can handle.
幸亏我另外两个孩子傻得像头驴
Thankfully,he blessed me with two other children who are dumb as soup.
抱歉 盖博豪斯博士 您在忙吗?
Excuse me,dr.Gablehauser,are you busy?
实际上...
Well,actually...
谢尔顿 他只是在乱画而已
sheldon,he's just doodlin'.
进来
Get in here.
盖博豪斯博士
Dr.Gablehauser.
库珀博士
Dr.Cooper.
说吧宝贝 天要黑了
Let's go,baby-- we're losing daylight.
你知道 几周前我们第一次见面时
as you know,several weeks ago in our first encounter,
我们可能没给彼此留下好印象 我称你为白痴
we may have gotten off on the wrong foot when I called you an idiot.
我只想跟你道歉...
And I just wanted to say that I was wrong...
指出这一点是我不对
to point it out.
抱歉 我们还不认识
I'm sorry,we haven't been introduced.
艾瑞克·盖博豪斯博士
Dr.Eric gablehauser.
我叫玛丽·库珀 是谢尔顿的妈妈
Mary cooper,sheldon's mom.
不可能吧
Now,that's impossible--
你怀他的时候还是个少女吧
you must have had him when you were a teenager.
你嘴真甜
Oh,aren't you sweet.
他父亲过世了
His father's dead.
- 最近? - 够久的了
- Recently? - Long enough.
请坐
Please.
谢尔顿 你不该去上班啊?
sheldon,shouldn't you be working?
好的
Okay.
怎么样?
Hey,how did it go?
我可以回来上班了
I got my job back.
真的? 怎么回事?
Really? What happened?
我不太清楚
I'm not quite sure.
其中包含的人类经验我从未经历过
It involves a part of the human experience that has always eluded me.
那还真是缩小范围了
Well,that narrows it down.
我为你骄傲 宝贝
I'm very proud of you,honey.
你今天表现出了极大的勇气
You showed a lot of courage today.
谢谢你 妈妈
Thanks,mom.
妈?
Mom?
盖博豪斯博士会是我的新爸爸吗?
Is dr.Gablehauser going to be my new daddy?
看看再说吧
We'll see.
好梦
Sleep tight.